Hi, I'm Ted Mosby
你好   我是泰德·莫斯比
and exactly 45 days from now,
确切地说从现在开始的45天
you and I are gonna meet,
确切地说从现在开始的45天   我会遇见你
and we're gonna fall in love.
我们会相爱
And we're gonna get married,and
我们会走进婚姻的殿堂
we're gonna have two kids,
我们会走进婚姻的殿堂   还会有2个小孩
We're gonna love them and each other so much.
我们会非常爱他们以及对方
All that is 45 days away.
这些都就差45天
But I'm here now,
但是我现在就来了
I guess because,
我想是因为
I want these extra 45 days, with you,
我想要这额外的45天
I want each one of them.
和你在一起我每一天都不想错过
Look, if I can't have them, I'll take the 45 seconds before your boyfriend shows up and punches me in the face.
如果我不能拥有这45天   在你男朋友出现并且给我一拳之前我就浪费这45秒钟
Because, I love you, I'm always gonna love you to the end of my days, and beyond.
因为我爱你   我会爱着你直到我生命的终点   直到永远